Downloaded from YTS.MX
从 YTS.MX 下载
Official YIFY movies site:
YIFY 电影官方网站：YTS.MX
I'll be late...
我会迟到...
So. Let's go!
所以。 我们走吧！
Good morning.
早上好。
Good morning, Taras.
早上好，塔拉斯。
- Good morning! - Good afternoon!
- 早上好！ - 下午好！
Good morning!
早上好！
Good...
好的...
Good afternoon.
下午好。
Good morning!
早上好！
- Is that my journal? - Yes, take it.
- 那是我的日记吗？ - 是的，拿着它。
Mykola, you have something on your cheek.
Mykola，你的脸颊上有东西。
Yanukovych refused to sign an agreement with the EU
亚努科维奇拒绝与欧盟签署协议，并为改善与俄罗斯的关系制定了路线。
The largest protest took place on Maidan in Kyiv,
最大规模的抗议发生在基辅的
the special forces killed more than 100 protesters.
Maidan，特种部队杀死了 100 多名抗议者。
Look, a sniper...
看，狙击手...
President of Ukraine, Viktor Yanukovych fled to Russia,
乌克兰总统维克托·亚努科维奇逃往俄罗斯，
leaving his post as Commander-in-Chief.
辞去总司令的职务。
Crimea was completely captured
克里米亚被完全俘虏并置于俄罗斯联邦的控制之下。
CRIMEA
克里米亚
Velocity is a physical quantity
速度是一个物理量
that characterizes the motion
表征运动的
and distance that an object travels per unit of time.
以及物体每单位时间行进的距离。
The velocity is calculated
计算速度
by the formula V=S/t.
由公式 V=S/t。
Where V is the speed...
其中V是速度...
- Are you a moron? - Shut your mouth, faggot!
- 你是个白痴吗？ - 闭嘴，基佬！
Ivan...
伊万...
S is distance.
S是距离。
And t is time.
t 是时间。
Can you hit in the same place again?
你能再次击中同一个地方吗？
RESET TIMER?
重置定时器？
0.9 seconds.
0.9 秒。
I measured a distance of seven meters.
我测量了七米的距离。
Ivan, what is the speed?
伊万，速度是多少？
Taras...
塔拉斯...
7.8 meters per second.
每秒 7.8 米。
Yes.
是的。
It was at this speed
就在这个速度
that Ivan spat out a piece of paper.
伊凡吐出一张纸。
Well, Ivan...
嗯，伊万...
if the time is not 0.9, but 0.7
如果时间不是 0.9，而是 0.7
at the same distance...
在相同的距离...
What would the speed be?
速度会是多少？
Write the answer on the board.
把答案写在黑板上。
Is there an answer?
有答案吗？
Now it's clear what you are distracted by...
现在很清楚你被什么分散了注意力......
Goodbye.
再见。
Goodbye, Taras.
再见，塔拉斯。
Listen, digger...
听着，挖掘机...
I'm sorry?
对不起？
You're a stranger here, get out.
你在这里是个陌生人，滚出去。
Lyosha, are you ready?
廖沙，你准备好了吗？
Yes.
是的。
The Voronenko family are the first eco-settlers in Donbas.
沃罗年科家族是顿巴斯的第一批生态定居者。
A year ago, they registered a two-hectare plot of land
一年前，他们登记了一块两公顷的土地
near Horlivka and moved to live in a field.
在 Horlivka 附近，搬到了一块田地里。
Mykola has three higher education degrees, mathematician, physicist, and ecologist.
Mykola拥有三个高等教育学位，数学家、物理学家和生态学家。
Explain what caused you to take such a radical step?
解释一下是什么让你采取了如此激进的步骤？
As an ecologist, I understand that difficult times await us.
作为一名生态学家，我明白困难时期正等着我们。
Only by changing the harmful way of life to an ecological one,
只有将有害的生活方式转变为生态的生活方式，
can we have a chance to save the planet and ourselves.
我们有机会拯救地球和我们自己吗？
How long do you plan to live here?
你打算在这里住多久？
We want to have and raise a child here.
我们想在这里生孩子。
Is your wife pregnant?
你老婆怀孕了吗？
Yes.
是的。
This means everything will work out just fine.
这意味着一切都会好起来的。
Tell me, what is this sign?
告诉我，这个标志是什么？
This is our ancestral sign.
这是我们祖先的标志。
And what does it mean?
这是什么意思？
Paw of a white raven.
白色乌鸦的爪子。
Will you tell me?
你会告诉我吗？
- This is... an ancient... - Get the microphone closer.
- 这是... 一个古老的... - 把麦克风靠近一点。
Let me hold it.
让我拿着。
...legend...
...传奇...
Raven created the world out of darkness, waving his wings.
乌鸦从黑暗中创造了世界，挥舞着翅膀。
And the world is a black ocean with a shore,
世界是黑色的海洋，有岸，
where people will soon come to live.
人们很快就会来到这里居住。
The raven, feeling pity for the people,
乌鸦同情人类，将海洋的咸水变成淡水和食物，
but in return...
但作为回报...
sacrifices its snow-white feathers.
牺牲了它雪白的羽毛。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Lesha, stop.
莱莎，停下。
Come on in, now I'll show you inside...
进来吧，现在我带你进去……
And this is a windmill.
这是一个风车。
I can tell you later about it, by the way, I made it myself.
我可以稍后告诉你，顺便说一句，我自己做的。
Shall we start with a dynamo machine?
我们从发电机开始吗？
I'll show you how it works...
我会告诉你它是如何工作的......
See?
看？
Lyosha, film just a few more details and these sketches.
Lyosha，拍摄更多细节和这些草图。
And you're not afraid to give birth here?
而且你不怕在这里生孩子吗？
No, I'm not afraid.
不，我不害怕。
Hmm...
唔...
Lena,
莉娜，
- I hope we are done? - Yes, we're done.
- 我希望我们完成了？ - 是的，我们完成了。
- I haven't shown you everything yet-- - Nikolai, thank you, we've had enough.
- 我还没有向你展示所有内容-- Nikolai，谢谢，我们已经受够了。
Two crazy people.
两个疯子。
Something fell out.
有什么东西掉了出来。
We do not throw trash here.
我们不在这里扔垃圾。
Goodbye.
再见。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Don't worry,
不用担心，
someday everything will come back to normal.
总有一天一切都会恢复正常。
Come with me, my dear love
跟我来，我亲爱的
To a place with shining stars
去一个星光灿烂的地方
There are rivers, mountains live on love
有江山有爱
The birds sing for us
鸟儿为我们歌唱
Your eyes are shining like emeralds
你的眼睛像翡翠一样闪闪发光
And disappeared In the misfortune of summer
消失在夏天的不幸中
I will give you the whole world
我会给你整个世界
And a daughter with the name Nastya
还有一个名叫娜斯佳的女儿
And a daughter with the name...
还有一个叫这个名字的女儿...
Nastya...
娜斯佳...
This is for you from us.
这是我们给你的。
Your Little Angel.
你的小天使。
Will protect you.
会保护你。
Buriy, we pass the line.
Buriy，我们过线了。
Confirmed. Chevrons.
确认的。 雪佛龙。
CAUTION! STATE BORDER OF UKRAINE. NO PASSAGE.
警告！ 乌克兰国界。 没有通道。
Get up, be fast!
起来，快点！
Yes, I'm coming, I'm coming...
是的，我来了，我来了……
Bye.
再见。
Oh, a normal engine!
哦，一个普通的引擎！
Flying!
飞行！
I'm flying...
我在飞翔...
Yes, everything was canceled.
是的，一切都被取消了。
No, I don't know...
不，我不知道...
Maybe it won't be...
或许不会……
Yes, I'll close it.
是的，我会关闭它。
This morning, an unknown bus stopped
今天早上，一辆不知名的巴士在顿涅茨克地区的霍利夫卡警察局附近停下。
It is also noted that armed militants in balaclavas
还值得注意的是，巴拉克拉法帽的武装武装分子
and pro-Russian activists
和亲俄活动家
continue to maintain the buildings of regional state administrations
继续维护斯洛维扬斯克、克拉马托尔斯克和顿涅茨克的地区国家行政机关大楼。
And...
和...
It just became clear that special forces of GUR
很明显，俄罗斯联邦 GUR 特种部队参加了
in the capture of the Rada Verkhovna of Crimea.
在捕获克里米亚的最高拉达。
Take your hands off of her!
把你的手从她身上拿开！
Who are you?
你是谁？
Bitch!
婊子！
What are you doing here, khokhlyara?
你在这里做什么，霍赫利亚拉？
I'm a teacher, I live here.
我是老师，我住在这里。
Are you a pacifist or something?
你是和平主义者还是什么？
- Who is he? - My husband.
- 他是谁？ - 我的老公。
In Russian, fuck, just talk!
用俄语，他妈的，只是说话！
Husband...
丈夫...
Don't touch her, she is pregnant!
别碰她，她怀孕了！
And what is this?
这是什么？
Those are my drawings.
这些是我的图纸。
Look at her face, she's definitely a spy!
看她的脸，绝对是间谍！
Stand!
站立！
Don't squeal!
不要尖叫！
Everyone, let's go.
大家，我们走吧。
What about him?
那么他呢？
We are leaving, I said.
我们要走了，我说。
Bitch!
婊子！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Get in the car quickly.
赶紧上车。
Please don't die...
请不要死...
Don't die, I'm here...
不要死，我在这里……
I'm here with you. No, no...
我在这儿陪你。 不，不...
No!
不！
Local?
当地的？
Documents?
文件？
In the bag.
在包里。
Who is she?
她是谁？
Wife.
妻子。
Mykola Voronenko...
米科拉·沃罗年科...
Looks like he is ours.
看来他是我们的了。
Come on.
来吧。
I don't care what happened there!
我不在乎那里发生了什么！
Why the fuck is he here?
他他妈怎么会在这里？
So, I should have left him in the middle of the field?
所以，我应该把他留在场地中央吗？
I do not understand. And if it's their spy?
我不明白。 如果是他们的间谍呢？
Have you thought about that?
你有想过吗？
Well, of course, you haven't thought about it.
好吧，当然，你没有考虑过。
Your head just doesn't work that way.
你的脑袋不是那样工作的。
But you are clearly not aware of that.
但你显然没有意识到这一点。
So, listen to me carefully. Take him away from here as far as...
所以，仔细听我说。 带他离开这里，直到……
Stop...
停止...
Did you blindfold him when you drove him to us?
你开车送他来我们的时候有没有蒙上他的眼睛？
What? Do you have no brain at all?
什么？ 你根本就没有脑子吗？
You leaked our base to him, you idiot!
你把我们的基地泄露给他了，你这个白痴！
Should I shoot him now?
我现在应该射他吗？
Ah, go away... you motherfucker!
啊，走开……你这个混蛋！
Skinny,
瘦骨嶙峋的，
what did I tell you?
我告诉你什么了？
Go to the toilet with a weapon in your hand!
拿着武器去厕所！
That's right!
没错！
Why are you reaching for your gun?
你为什么伸手去拿你的枪？
Do you want to shoot yourself?
你想自己开枪吗？
We need to drive them out.
我们需要把他们赶出去。
What did he say?
他说什么？
I want to drive them out of our land.
我想把他们赶出我们的土地。
- Falcons flutter in the sky.
- 猎鹰在天空中飞舞。
- Our squad flies into battle.
- 我们的小队飞入战场。
- We will defeat the enemies.
- 我们将击败敌人。
- Although they crawl from all sides.
- 虽然他们从四面八方爬行。
Come on, guys, come on.
来吧，伙计们，来吧。
Faster. Tempo, tempo I said! Come on!
快点。 节奏，我说的节奏！ 来吧！
Bad!
坏的！
As you were!
和你一样！
Show him.
让他看。
That's it, comrade!
就是这样，同志！
Come on, come on, men, faster!
来吧，来吧，伙计们，快点！
Thirty-three,
三十三，
thirty-four...
三十四...
- Thirty-five! - Keep the body straight.
- 三十五！  - 保持身体挺直。
Thirty-six!
三十六！
Thirty-seven!
三十七！
And now have a rest!
现在休息一下！
Well, do you enjoy being here as a pacifist?
好吧，作为和平主义者，你喜欢在这里吗？
Yes, sir, Mr. Commander!
是的，长官，指挥官先生！
I'm glad to hear that.
我很高兴听到这个消息。
Permission to speak, sir, Mr. Commander!
长官，指挥官先生，请允许发言！
Permitted.
允许。
I'm not a pacifist, Mr. Commander.
我不是和平主义者，指挥官先生。
My code name is Raven!
我的代号是乌鸦！
Dead Raven!
死乌鸦！
I said one and a half!
我说一个半！
This code name still needs to be earned, comrade.
同志，这个代号还是要挣来的。
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
Yes, sir, Mr. Commander!
是的，长官，指挥官先生！
Chief.
首席。
Crazy?
疯狂的？
Hey, bud, you want tea?
嘿，伙计，你想喝茶吗？
And you?
你呢？
Don't sleep!
别睡觉！
Quickly, quickly...
快快快...
Girls, don't get caught in your bras!
女孩们，不要被你的胸罩夹住！
The war will come to an end while you are still swarming like a pacifist!
当你仍然像和平主义者一样蜂拥而至时，战争就会结束！
Start again! Disassemble!
重新开始！ 拆卸！
Quickly! Let's not linger!
迅速地！ 让我们不要流连忘返！
Twenty-eight,
二十八、
twenty-nine...
二十九...
- Lower! - Forty...
- 降低！ - 四十...
Attention!
注意力！
There are not enough snipers at the front.
前线的狙击手不够多。
Volunteers organize free courses. Are you interested?
志愿者组织免费课程。 你感兴趣吗？
Bad, Klym, Dunay, good.
坏的，克利姆，杜内，好。
What? A pacifist? You too? Sit down.
什么？ 和平主义者？ 你也是？ 坐下。
I, private Raven, ask to join!
我，私人乌鸦，请求加入！
Listen, you don't know how to remove a magazine from the AK!
听着，你不知道如何从 AK 中取出杂志！
Which of you is a sniper?
你们谁是狙击手？
Let me show you!
我来给你展示！
Interesting. And what can you show us?
有趣的。 你能告诉我们什么？
Disassembly-assembly of AK in 20 seconds.
在 20 秒内拆装 AK。
In 20 seconds?
在 20 秒内？
This should be fun.
这应该是有趣的。
Well,
出色地，
you asked yourself.
你问自己。
Come on.
来吧。
Well, warrior... ready?
好吧，战士……准备好了吗？
Well.
出色地。
Come on!
来吧！
Congratulations to Private Raven...
恭喜私人乌鸦...
Eighteen seconds!
十八秒！
Well done! Bravo!
做得好！ 太棒了！
Well done!
做得好！
That's what I understand.
这就是我的理解。
Find him one SKS.
给他找一个SKS。
Right turn! March!
右转！ 行进！
Nobody likes snipers
没有人喜欢狙击手
because they are insidious and elegant.
因为它们阴险而优雅。
There are no forbidden methods of waging war for them.
对他们发动战争没有被禁止的方法。
Professional snipers work in disguise without modern special equipment.
专业狙击手在没有现代特殊设备的情况下伪装工作。
Their position is almost impossible to detect.
他们的位置几乎不可能被发现。
Especially...
尤其...
if no shots are heard or they are hidden under another noise.
如果没有听到枪声或者它们被隐藏在另一个噪音之下。
Excuse me,
打扰一下，
what does that mean?
这意味着什么？
In order not to get caught, the sniper fires his shot
为了不被抓住，狙击手在机关枪射击或爆炸声中开枪。
Next!
下一个！
Budkevych.
布德克维奇。
- Next! - Dunaevsky.
- 下一个！ - 杜纳耶夫斯基。
Next!
下一个！
Voronenko.
沃罗年科。
- What is this? - A horse in a coat!
- 这是什么？ - 穿大衣的马！
This is SKS. "Simonov's self-loading carbine"!
这是SKS。  “西蒙诺夫的自动装弹卡宾枪”！
Next!
下一个！
This is a mistake.
这是个错误。
I have to have an SVD like everybody else.
我必须像其他人一样拥有 SVD。
Dear, no need for songs here! Is it a circus for you here?
亲爱的，这里不需要歌曲！ 这里适合你吗？
Do I look like a clown?
我看起来像小丑吗？
This is, the fucking, army!
这就是，他妈的，军队！
Your task is to pick up the fucking gun and get the fuck out of here!
你的任务是拿起他妈的枪，让他妈的离开这里！
Can I go?
我可以去吗？
What is this... Blaster, fuck!
这是什么……爆破，操！
And we are all space pirates here, for fuck's sake!
我们都是太空海盗，看在他妈的份上！
Don't giggle!
不要傻笑！
Soldiers, I do not repeat anything twice.
士兵们，我不会重复任何事情。
Nobody is going to jerk off with you here!
没有人会在这里和你混蛋！
Next!
下一个！
Look, Raven.
看，乌鸦。
Will you give me your Blaster for a shot?
你能给我你的冲击波吗？
The basic rule of a sniper is to remain invisible under any circumstances.
狙击手的基本规则是在任何情况下都保持隐形。
If you move, assume you've been killed.
如果你移动，假设你已经被杀了。
Moved.
搬家了。
Minus one point.
减一分。
Minus.
减。
Have a look at your 1963 Dragunov sniper rifle.
看看你的 1963 年 Dragunov 狙击步枪。
With its obsolete 7.62 by 54 mm ammunition,
凭借其过时的 7.62 x 54 毫米弹药，
it has a working distance
它有一个工作距离
of approximately 600 meters.
约600米。
In contrast,
相比之下，
modern 8.6 by 70 Lapua Magnum
现代 8.6 x 70 Lapua Magnum
or 12.7 by 99 BMG...
或 12.7 x 99 BMG...
rifles hit targets...
步枪击中目标...
even at 2,000 meters.
即使在 2,000 米处。
And how far does your rifle shoot?
你的步枪能射多远？
Remington 308 caliber has a working distance of...
Remington 308 机芯的工作距离为...
about 800 meters.
约800米。
And if the enemy has a better shot?
如果敌人有更好的射击？
Then you are unlucky.
那你倒霉了。
This is called a ballistic vulnerability.
这称为弹道漏洞。
But it's not a rifle that makes a sniper dangerous...
但让狙击手变得危险的并不是步枪……
But his intelligence and endurance.
但他的智慧和耐力。
The next task...
下一个任务...
be ready.
准备好。
The sniper must always be stable and focused.
狙击手必须始终保持稳定和专注。
Charge!
收费！
Take aim.
瞄准。
Ready.
准备好。
One, two, three... Fire!
一、二、三……火！
Plus.
加。
Ready.
准备好。
One, two, three... Fire!
一、二、三……火！
Plus.
加。
Ready.
准备好。
One, two, three... Fire!
一、二、三……火！
Minus.
减。
It's not possible with such a firearm!
这样的枪支是不可能的！
Some succeeded.
有的成功了。
One of the important skills a sniper
狙击手必须具备的一项重要技能是能够在脑海中快速计算。
Your eyes will be occupied with observing things.
你的眼睛会专注于观察事物。
Forget about the calculator.
忘记计算器。
To determine the distance,
要确定距离，必须将对象的大小乘以 1000
and divide by the number of points in sight.
并除以视线中的点数。
So the task is to determine the distance to the KAMAZ.
因此，任务是确定到 KAMAZ 的距离。
The height of the KAMAZ is 3.45...
KAMAZ 的高度是 3.45...
and has seven points,
并且有七个点，
The height of the armored personnel carrier...
装甲运兵车的高度...
is 2.35...
是 2.35...
and has 2.5 points.
并且有 2.5 分。
Tank width...
油箱宽度...
3.46...
3.46...
Allow me...
让我...
Is something unclear, Raven?
有什么不清楚的吗，瑞文？
- I want to give the answer. - Try it.
- 我想给出答案。 - 试试看。
Distance to KAMAZ is 493 meters.
到 KAMAZ 的距离是 493 米。
That's right.
没错。
940 meters and 804 and a half.
940米804半。
To the armored personnel carrier and to the tank accordingly.
到装甲运兵车和相应的坦克。
Not bad, Raven.
不错，乌鸦。
Before the shot, everyone should call his code out loud.
在开枪之前，每个人都应该大声喊出他的代码。
"Code green" for I can shoot.
“代码绿色”，因为我可以拍摄。
"Code red" for I can't shoot.
“红色代码”因为我不能射击。
Get ready!
做好准备！
Attention!
注意力！
Three,
三，
two, one...
二，一……
Code green.
代码绿色。
Bob, minus.
鲍勃，减去。
Bad, plus.
不好，加。
Yartur, plus.
亚图尔，加。
Klym, plus.
克利姆，加。
Mor, minus.
莫尔，减号。
Dunay, plus.
杜内，加。
Raven, minus...
乌鸦，减...
Exam completed. Discharge everyone's weapons.
考试完毕。 释放每个人的武器。
Raven, haven't you heard the command?
瑞文，你没听到命令吗？
The exam is not over yet.
考试还没有结束。
Why is that?
这是为什么？
I didn't shoot.
我没拍。
Are you going to wait for dawn?
你要等天亮吗？
The code is green!
代码是绿色的！
Wow, holy Blaster!
哇，神圣的冲击波！
Plus three, Raven.
再加上三个，乌鸦。
Thank you for waiting.
谢谢你的等待。
Klym!
克利姆！
Yes sir!
是的先生！
Second-class.
二等。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
I serve the Ukrainian people!
我为乌克兰人民服务！
Dunay!
多奈！
Yes sir!
是的先生！
Third-class. Congratulations.
三等。 恭喜。
I serve the Ukrainian people!
我为乌克兰人民服务！
Raven!
掠夺！
Yes sir!
是的先生！
First-class.
一流的。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
I serve the Ukrainian people!
我为乌克兰人民服务！
- Bad! - Yes sir!
- 坏的！ - 是的先生！
Second-class. Congratulations...
二等。 恭喜...
Tell me, why did this happen?
告诉我，为什么会这样？
Why is it that my world Is not enough for your world?
为什么我的世界还不够你的世界？
The two of us touched for a moment
我们两个有接触
And time passes us by craftily
时间悄悄地从我们身边流逝
Nobody knows where to go now
没人知道现在该去哪里
Nobody is waiting at home
没人在家等
Dive in, love your will
潜入，爱你的意志
But don't get lost in the pain
但不要迷失在痛苦中
And awaken, awaken strength in yourself
唤醒，唤醒你自己的力量
Build strength in yourself
建立自己的力量
My dear, my dear...
亲爱的，亲爱的……
I wish we had wings...
我希望我们有翅膀...
We need to go to the zero line to our positions.
我们需要去零线到我们的位置。
Here they captured our checkpoint on the bridge.
他们在这里占领了我们在桥上的检查站。
I don't have enough people...
我没有足够的人...
We need to clean up before they get strengthened.
我们需要在它们得到加强之前进行清理。
What do they have?
他们有什么？
No armor, nothing heavy. We'll handle it.
没有盔甲，没有重物。 我们会处理的。
And the machine gunners?
机枪手呢？
Pokemon and RPK.
口袋妖怪和RPK。
Okay, take the snipers and assault team.
好吧，带上狙击手和突击队。
Plus.
加。
- Hello, guys. - We wish you good health!
- 大家好。 - 我们祝您身体健康！
- Voron... - Aye, sir.
- 沃伦... - 是的，先生。
Pack up your staff.
收拾你的员工。
Yes, sir, Lieutenant Colonel.
是的，长官，中校。
Third in position.
排名第三。
First in position.
位居第一。
The second is ready.
第二个准备好了。
What is the distance?
距离是多少？
400 meters.
400米。
Two up.
上两个。
Your machine gunner is on the left,
你的机枪手在左边，
I'm working on the right.
我在右边工作。
Plus.
加。
Ready.
准备好。
Prepared.
准备好了。
Countdown.
倒数。
Plus.
加。
Two,
二，
one...
一...
- Car on 9! - Stop!
- 9 号车！ - 停止！
Cap, machine. Two civilians.
帽子，机器。 两个平民。
Get out of the car!
从车里出去！
Documents.
文件。
- Give me my passport! - Watch your hands, bitch!
- 把我的护照给我！ - 小心你的手，婊子！
Wait.
等待。
Plus.
加。
Attention!
注意力！
Countdown.
倒数。
Three...
三...
two...
二...
one!
一！
Contact.
接触。
Get back, bitch!
回去吧，婊子！
The target is a militant behind the hostage.
目标是人质背后的武装分子。
I operate near the hostage.
我在人质附近行动。
Lie down, stupid!
躺下，笨蛋！
Hit. Clean!
打。 干净的！
Congratulations on your first successful task.
恭喜你完成了第一个成功的任务。
Clean!
干净的！
Come on.
来吧。
Hello guys.
大家好。
- Congratulations, boys! - Hello.
- 恭喜，孩子们！ - 你好。
- Are Klym and Dunay here? - I am not sure.
- Klym 和 Dunay 在吗？ - 我不知道。
Bad!
坏的！
Hello.
你好。
Where are Klym and Dunay?
Klym 和 Dunay 在哪里？
On the mission.
在执行任务。
Dunay...
杜奈...
Where is Klym?
克利姆在哪里？
What did you find out?
你发现了什么？
The medic said that the bullet in Klym's body opened like a flower,
医生说，Klym 身上的子弹像花朵一样裂开，
some fragments passed through,
一些碎片穿过，
and others got stuck in the armor plate.
其他人被卡在装甲板上。
The guy had no chance.
这家伙没有机会。
The vehicle breaks through,
车辆突破，
what can we say about the body...
我们能对身体说些什么...
they want to demoralize us.
他们想让我们士气低落。
So that's it.
就是这样。
We need to quickly occupy our trench at the zero line,
我们需要迅速占领我们撤离的零线处的战壕。
Take a detour along this forest strip, the DRG enemy was noticed here.
沿着这条森林地带绕道而行，这里发现了DRG敌人。
I'll give you an assault group to cover.
我会给你一个突击小组来掩护。
As you occupy the trench,
当你占领战壕时，留意他们在附近的位置。
Just be careful,
小心点，
there may be a sniper somewhere.
某处可能有狙击手。
If it's clean,
如果干净，
I'll send a company to strengthen it.
我会派一个公司来加强它。
Follow.
跟随。
Plus.
加。
Cossacks, five minutes left.
哥萨克，还有五分钟。
Report...
报告...
First clear.
先说清楚。
Plus.
加。
Distance 120.
距离 120。
Cap, third post. I see a group of five.
帽，第三个职位。 我看到一组五个。
Russian uniform, confidently going on the green to meet you, do you roger?
俄罗斯制服，自信满满地在果岭上迎接你，你知道吗？
Plus.
加。
The goal will be in 25.
目标将在 25 岁。
Twenty...
二十...
Fifteen...
十五...
Ten,
十，
nine...
九...
Ivan?
伊万?
Six,
六，
five,
五，
four,
四、
three,
三，
two,
二，
one.
一。
Fire!
火！
Good job.
好工作。
- We're done, finish it. - Plus-plus.
- 我们完成了，完成它。  - 加加。
Who is Ivan?
伊万是谁？
My former student from Horlivka.
我以前在 Horlivka 的学生。
He made his choice.
他做出了自己的选择。
As did I...
和我一样...
Huh, yeah. Piece of shit.
嗯，是的。 一坨屎。
So what's up?
那么怎么了？
Stretches checked.
检查拉伸。
It will not be possible to climb through quietly.
不可能悄悄地爬过去。
Who is in the photo?
照片里是谁？
Family.
家庭。
Can I have a look?
我可以看一下吗？
My wife Svitlana
我的妻子斯维特拉娜
and daughters, Vika and Myroslava.
和女儿维卡和米罗斯拉娃。
Do the kids know where you are now?
孩子们知道你现在在哪里吗？
No.
不。
They think that I'm on a business trip.
他们认为我在出差。
My wife and I agreed that if they know less, they will sleep better.
我和妻子一致认为，如果他们知道的更少，他们会睡得更好。
That's why she's worried about everyone there.
这就是为什么她担心那里的每个人。
Got it.
知道了。
Is this your amulet?
这是你的护身符吗？
This is my...
这是我的...
family.
家庭。
Their positions are here.
他们的位置在这里。
Keep an eye on them.
留意他们。
Yes, I understand. Crystal.
是的我明白。 水晶。
Yes, of course, Nikolai Ivanych,
是的，当然，尼古拉·伊凡内奇，
we will do everything, don't worry.
我们会尽一切努力，别担心。
On the other side, we need more.
另一方面，我们需要更多。
Five minutes. Come on, come on.
5分钟。 好啦好啦。
Understood, I'm working.
明白了，我在工作。
Are the weapons checked?
武器检查了吗？
Batteries, walkie-talkies,
电池、对讲机、
- first aid kits. - We have it!
- 急救箱。 - 我们有它！
Everything is there!
一切都在那里！
Take off the flag, fuck...
拿下国旗，操...
- Exactly! Shoot, bro! - Come on.
- 确切地！ 开枪吧兄弟！ - 来吧。
Just cut the normal branches, why are you dragging this shit.
把正常的树枝剪掉，你为什么要拖这个狗屎。
Here they have two.
这里他们有两个。
Here is a machine gun and a sniper pair.
这是一挺机枪和一对狙击手。
- Will you cover-up? - Yeah.
- 你会掩饰吗？  - 是的。
Do you need an assistant?
你需要助手吗？
I'll handle it.
我会处理的。
- Everything is ready. - Let's get everyone inside.
- 一切都准备好了。 - 让每个人都进去。
- Get inside! - Start engine!
- 进去！ - 启动引擎！
- Let's go!
- 我们走吧！
At 11 o'clock there is a car.
11点有车。
I see.
我懂了。
Two militants near the car.
两名武装分子靠近汽车。
Continue observation.
继续观察。
A fighter with a machine gun.
有机关枪的战斗机。
The code is green. I can work!
代码是绿色的。 我能工作！
I do not allow you to.
我不允许你这样做。
Keep observing.
继续观察。
A fighter with a machine gun.
有机关枪的战斗机。
The code is green. I can work!
代码是绿色的。 我能工作！
Put on the fuse!
装上保险丝！
A fighter with a machine gun! The code is green! I'm shooting!
有机关枪的战斗机！ 代码是绿色的！ 我在射击！
Put on the safety. That is an order!
穿上保险。 那是命令！
Motherfucker!
混蛋！
I have 200!
我有200！
Sniper at 10 o'clock!
10点狙击手！
Sniper! On the tenth! Distance 2,000.
狙击手！ 第十日！ 距离 2,000。
The first minus.
第一个减号。
Second in the sector K4.
在 K4 领域排名第二。
Yes. We are working.
是的。 我们正在工作。
I asked at the top...
我在楼上问...
Secret services will look for the killer of the Cap.
特勤局将寻找帽子的杀手。
When there is information,
有信息的时候，
I'll call you
我会打电话给你
and you will deal with it.
你会处理它。
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
Dismissed.
被解雇。
Captain...
队长...
It's time for us.
现在是我们的时候了。
Yakut.
雅库特。
What do you have?
你有什么？
How long will I be lying here?
我要在这里躺多久？
I won't be able to wash off this shit for a week.
我将无法洗掉这个狗屎一个星期。
Be patient, Makar. You will lie in my shit all my life.
耐心点，马卡尔。 你会一辈子躺在我的屎里。
Fuck off.
滚蛋。
I waved everything.
我挥了挥手。
I will crawl to you.
我会爬到你身边。
Makar, respond.
马卡尔，回应。
Fuck. Where are you, have you fallen?
他妈的。 你在哪里，你跌倒了吗？
You, bitch.
你，婊子。
...The third-largest nuclear arsenal
...第三大核武库
in the world.
在世界上。
And in 1994 a memorandum was signed
1994年，乌克兰、俄罗斯、英国和美国签署了一份备忘录……
That's right.
没错。
The memorandum on non-proliferation guaranteed Ukraine's independence,
不扩散备忘录保证乌克兰的独立，
sovereignty, and borders.
主权和边界。
We all know how Russia respects the borders of other states...
我们都知道俄罗斯如何尊重其他国家的边界​​......
So the solution to this problem...
所以这个问题的解决方案...
BRIGADE COMMANDER
旅长
Speaking.
请讲。
It lit up near Horlivka.
它在霍利夫卡附近亮了起来。
He fired two of our scouts.
他解雇了我们的两个球探。
Was it in a wide range?
范围很广吗？
Yes.
是的。
The first, two days ago. The second, today.
第一次，两天前。 第二个，今天。
From one position?
从一个位置？
Not by the phone. At the meeting. Get ready.
不是通过电话。 在会议上。 做好准备。
ID?
ID？
Drive.
驾驶。
Open it.
打开它。
Code name Elbrus, second-class.
代号厄尔布鲁士，二等。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
- Beast, third-class, congratulations. - Yeah.
- 野兽，三等，恭喜。  - 是的。
- Ray, third-class... - Yes.
- 雷，三等舱... - 是的。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
- Congratulations. - I serve the Ukrainian people!
- 恭喜。 - 我为乌克兰人民服务！
- How are you? - Alive.
- 你好吗？ - 活着。
Got you this.
给你这个。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
- Hello! - Hi!
- 你好！
Cadets, at ease. Grab your stuff and get in the car.
学员，放心。 拿起你的东西，上车。
Raven...
掠夺...
Aye.
是的。
- Ready? - Yes sir.
- 准备好？ - 是的先生。
Follow me.
跟着我。
Attention to all.
注意所有。
Recently, intelligence provided us with information...
最近，情报为我们提供了信息……
Show the slide.
显示幻灯片。
Russian sniper. Call sign "Sery".
俄罗斯狙击手。 呼号“系列”。
Works with 12.7 over long distances, mostly 1.5 km.
适用于 12.7 长距离，主要是 1.5 公里。
The bullets are wide-ranging.
子弹范围很广。
He has already killed five of our snipers and three machine gunners.
他已经杀死了我们的五名狙击手和三名机枪手。
Show the site.
显示网站。
He publishes his videos to demoralize us.
他发布他的视频来打击我们的士气。
In one of these videos, is our Cap.
在其中一个视频中，是我们的 Cap。
Shit!
拉屎！
Yesterday our sniper
昨天我们的狙击手被装甲板之间的同一颗子弹杀死
near a chemical plant next to the river.
靠近河边的化工厂。
Today was the same, they hit in the same sector.
今天也是一样，他们打在同一个领域。
They didn't change position?
他们没有改变立场？
Cover it with mines.
用地雷覆盖它。
It won't work.
不起作用。
Raven, you are a local, explain to the guys.
瑞文，你是本地人，给大家解释一下。
There is a chlorine storage under pressure in the chemical plant.
化工厂有一个压力下的氯气储存器。
Well, fuck them. PTUR him to the damn mother.
好吧，操他们。 把他交给该死的母亲。
- Explosion of cylinders is guaranteed. - So what?
- 保证气瓶爆炸。 - 所以呢？
Environmental disaster.
环境灾难。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Is that clear to everyone?
大家都清楚吗？
The plan is as follows. Map.
计划如下。 地图。
There are a total of eight militants on the territory.
该领土上共有八名武装分子。
The sniper himself is probably in a building
狙击手本人可能在一座有氯气仓库的建筑物中。
Plus two of his observers are probably on the floors.
再加上他的两个观察员可能在地板上。
So,
所以，
the first pair of snipers takes the first fighter.
第一对狙击手拿下第一名战士。
The second and third are these targets.
第二个和第三个就是这些目标。
The fourth and fifth are these two.
第四和第五就是这两个。
And the final targets,
而最终的目标，
two observers...
两个观察者...
and Sery.
和系列。
What's the point? Anyway, we cannot shoot this chlorine under pressure.
重点是什么？ 无论如何，我们不能在压力下射出这种氯气。
Our task is to clear the access only.
我们的任务是仅清除访问权限。
And then what?
然后什么？
Then Raven climbs up to him.
然后乌鸦爬到他身边。
Questions?
问题？
Get ready.
做好准备。
Raven, status.
乌鸦, 地位.
Three hours.
三个小时。
Plus.
加。
First.
第一的。
In position.
在位。
Second.
第二。
Raven, status...
乌鸦，地位...
In position...
在位...
Ah, pacifist...
啊，和平主义者...
I should have shot you then...
那我应该开枪打死你...
- Clear. - Plus.
- 清除。 - 加号。
Attention, readiness. Report...
注意，准备。 报告...
First ready.
先准备好了。
Second ready.
二准备。
Third ready.
第三个准备好了。
Fifth ready...
五号准备...
I see the target, the code is green.
我看到了目标，代码是绿色的。
Countdown...
倒数...
Five,
五，四，
three,
三，二，
one.
一。
Whose fire?
谁的火？
Fuck if I know. The moron is watering somewhere.
他妈的，如果我知道。 白痴在某处浇水。
Report!
报告！
Clear.
清除。
- Raven, work. - Plus.
- 乌鸦，工作。 - 加号。
First.
第一的。
Second.
第二。
In place.
到位。
Report.
报告。
Group, report...
分组，报告...
Group, report.
分组，报告。
- There is no connection with the group. - Second, report to me.
- 与该组没有任何联系。 - 第二，向我报告。
Sery!
系列！
- Hold your position! - Yes.
- 保持你的立场！ - 是的。
Fuck.
他妈的。
- Second... - In place.
- 第二... - 到位。
- Brown. - Affirmative.
- 棕色的。 - 肯定的。
- I have one 200. - What happened?
- 我有一个 200。 - 发生了什么事？
Sniper.
狙击手。
Clear. What about the security group?
清除。 安全组呢？
No connection.
没有关联。
Got it. Ten minutes. Hold your position.
知道了。  10分钟。 保持你的立场。
Yes.
是的。
Second.
第二。
In place.
到位。
Return to your position and guard the entrance.
回到你的位置并守卫入口。
Yes.
是的。
Fuck...
他妈的...
Sery. Do you copy?
系列。 你抄吗？
Sery, arrived with a group. Do you copy?
Sery，与一群人一起到达。 你抄吗？
You shitbags will answer us for Crimea.
你们这些混蛋会为克里米亚回答我们的问题。
- Clean.
- 干净的。
Raven, the perimeter is clean.
乌鸦，外围很干净。
Plus.
加。
Let him stay with me...
让他留在我身边...
Guide your hand, Lord,
主啊，引导你的手，
to destroy all enemies...
消灭所有敌人……
on this land.
在这片土地上。